<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio Site - Aleks Petrov on Home</title>
    <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio Site - Aleks Petrov on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Well Production &amp; Project Economics Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project3/</guid>
      <description>Summary: PowerBI dashboard that incorporates well production data and oil prices over time. The dashboard visualizes and reports well production and revenue over time, as well as the project economics of the individual wells going forward. The dashboard includes net present value measures in order to determine profitability of the producing wells as well as scenario analysis in forecasting revenue. The goal of this dashboard is to test out forward looking analytical features in an oil &amp;amp; gas context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Well Production &amp; Project Economics Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project4test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project4test/</guid>
      <description>Summary: PowerBI dashboard that incorporates well production data and oil prices over time. The dashboard visualizes and reports well production and revenue over time, as well as the project economics of the individual wells going forward. The dashboard includes net present value measures in order to determine profitability of the producing wells as well as scenario analysis in forecasting revenue. The goal of this dashboard is to test out forward looking analytical features in an oil &amp;amp; gas context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Variance &amp; Transactions Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project1/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Dashboard that incorporates transaction-level data to assist in month-end variance from budget analysis. Utilized ERP Cloud (SAP HANA) in order to pull the relevant transaction data, the EPM (Hyperion) to pull budget data, and a SQL query to pull relevant invoice information. Then transformed and prepared the data with PowerQuery in PowerBI. Afterwards used DAX and PowerPivot in PowerBI to create a model. Finally used PowerBI to visualize the data and create a dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Personal Finances Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project2/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Excel model that incorporates personal financial information like expenses and budget data. Utilizing PowerQuery to extract and transform the data, PowerPivot to create a model with logic, and finally Excel to display the data in a dashboard for analysis. This model is an example of what I use to track my personal finances except it uses randomized data. Goal was to have an automatable report for easy analysis of personal financial data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by the finance side of businesses. I started off my pursuits in a bookkeeping role at a local corporation while in highschool and was exposed to all facets of the business. Going into college, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the privilege of taking many finance, accounting, and econometrics courses and have had internship opportunities which have expanded my horizons. I now hope to build my career in accounting/finance where I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to support the business and operations by providing meticulous reporting and analytical insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prospective Projects</title>
      <link>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aleks-petrov.github.io/portfolio/post/project0/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find projects that I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on or projects that I plan to work on in the future with short descriptions.
Freelance Project for Logistics Company Currently in the process of securing a freelance contract with a transportation logistics company to implement business intelligence and data analytics tools in order to improve their current processes.
Transactions Analytics Project In the process of creating analytical tools for the transactions reporting dashboard already posted in the portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
